export default
  {
    "questions": [
      {
        id: 1,
        question: 'Which of the following is an advantage of using JavaScript?',
        options: [
          'It is a lightweight language',
          'It is a multi-paradigm language',
          'It is an interpreted language',
          'It is an object-oriented language',
        ],

        answer: 'a',
      },
      {
        id: 2,
        question: 'Which of the following is not a JavaScript data type?',
        options: ['Boolean', 'Number', 'String', 'Object'],
        answer: 'd',
      },
      {
        id: 3,
        question: 'Which of the following is not a JavaScript operator?',
        options: ['new', 'delete', 'typeof', 'instanceof'],
        answer: 'b',
      },
      {
        id: 4,
        question: 'Which of the following is not a JavaScript function?',
        options: ['Boolean', 'Number', 'String', 'Object'],
        answer: 'a',
      },
      {
        id: 5,
        question: 'Which of the following is not a JavaScript loop?',
        options: ['while', 'for', 'do while', 'for in'],
        answer: 'c',
      },
      {
        id: 6,
        question:
          'Which of the following is not a JavaScript primitive data type?',
        options: ['Boolean', 'Number', 'String', 'Object'],
        answer: 'd',
      },
      {
        id: 7,
        question: 'Which of the following is not a JavaScript operator?',
        options: ['new', 'delete', 'typeof', 'instanceof'],
        answer: 'b',
      },
      {
        id: 8,
        question: 'Which of the following is not a JavaScript function?',
        options: ['Boolean', 'Number', 'String', 'Object'],
        answer: 'a',
      },
      {
        id: 9,
        question: 'Which of the following is not a JavaScript loop?',
        options: ['while', 'for', 'do while', 'for in'],
        answer: 'c',
      },
      {
        id: 10,
        question:
          'Which of the following is not a JavaScript primitive data type?',
        options: ['Boolean', 'Number', 'String', 'Object'],
        answer: 'd',
      },
    ],
  }
  ;
